Parks & Trails New York; Records apap362
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Parks & Trails New York Records
2004 June 10 - 2017 July 18
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
apap362
30.25 cubic ft.
217 captures
This collection documents the day-to-day activities of Parks & Trails New York, the leading statewide advocate for parks and trails in New York State.
Collection X
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Web Archives
Access
Access to this collection is restricted because it is unprocessed. Portions of the collection may contain recent administrative records and/or personally identifiable information. Please contact an archivist for more information.
Acquisition Information
All items in this collection were transferred to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives by Jackie Gonzales, Ph.D. of Parks & Trails New York in 2016 January.
Historical Note
Founded in 1985 as the New York Parks and Conservation Association, Parks & Trails New York (which assumed its current name in 2004) is the leading statewide advocate for parks and trails in New York State.
Scope and Contents
The collection includes correspondence, publications, annual reports, general subject files, park trails, and maps.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is unprocessed and is likely disorganized. Individual items may be difficult to find.
Web Archives; Wages -- New York (State); Parks & Trails New York
- Parks & Trails New York Website, 2004 June 10 - 2017 July 18; 1; 217 captures
  URL
  http://www.ptny.org/
  Access Requirements
  The item contains web archives preserved as WARC files. They must be access though web archival replay tools such as the "Wayback Machine." The links here direct you to files hosted by the Internet Archive, but you may also request WARC files.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Web crawling is managed through the Internet Archive's Archive-It service.
  This item is a seed within the Parks & Trails NY collection.
  Other seeds in this collection include: http://twitter.com/ptny/, http://www.facebook.com/parksandtrailsny/
  Archive-it Collection Details:
  created_date: 2016-08-25T19:10:39Z
  created_by: gwiedeman
  state: ACTIVE
  last_updated_date: 2016-09-26T23:39:07Z
  last_updated_by: system
  Web Collection
  - PTNY Welcome!, 2004 June 10
    Scope and Contents
    Meta tag for keywords: new york parks conservation association trails
    This crawl was performed by the Internet Archive, not the UAlbany web archiving program, so the provenance is unknown.
  - PTNY Main Page, 2004 December 2
    Meta tag for description: Statewide non-profit advocating for New York parks, greenways and trails; Annual Erie Canal Bike Tour; Trailfinder Maps; Newlstetter; Membership; Tourism
    Meta tag for keywords: Trails Parks
  - PTNY Main Page, 2004 December 16
  - PTNY Main Page, 2005 January 6
  - PTNY Main Page, 2005 January 27
  - PTNY Main Page, 2005 March 8
  - PTNY Main Page, 2005 March 31
  - PTNY Main Page, 2005 June 3
  - PTNY Main Page, 2005 June 16
  - PTNY Main Page, 2005 July 26
  - PTNY Main Page, 2005 August 14
  - PTNY Main Page, 2005 August 29
  - PTNY Main Page, 2005 October 16
  - PTNY Main Page, 2005 December 14
  - PTNY Main Page, 2006 February 2
  - PTNY Main Page, 2006 April 13
  - PTNY Main Page, 2006 April 20
  - PTNY Main Page, 2006 June 15
  - PTNY Main Page, 2006 July 17
  - PTNY Main Page, 2006 August 3
  - PTNY Main Page, 2006 August 22
  - PTNY Main Page, 2006 August 26
  - PTNY Main Page, 2006 September 2
  - PTNY Main Page, 2006 October 14
  - PTNY Main Page, 2006 December 5
  - PTNY Main Page, 2007 February 8
  - PTNY Main Page, 2007 February 23
  - PTNY Main Page, 2007 March 9
  - PTNY Main Page, 2007 July 16
    Meta tag for description: Statewide non-profit advocating for New York parks, greenways and trails; Annual Cycling the Erie Canal Bike Tour & Great Hudson Valley Pedal; Trailfinder Maps; Newsletters; Membership; bicycle; parks; trails; Tourism
  - PTNY Main Page, 2007 August 8
  - PTNY Main Page, 2007 September 13
  - PTNY Main Page, 2007 September 28
  - PTNY Main Page, 2007 October 12
  - PTNY Main Page, 2007 October 26
  - PTNY Main Page, 2007 November 27
  - PTNY Main Page, 2007 December 28
  - Parks & Trails New York - working to expand, protect and promote a network of parks, trails and open spaces throughout our state for use and enjoyment by all, 2008 April 10
    Meta tag for description: Statewide non-profit organization advocating for New York parks, greenways and trails; Annual Cycling the Erie Canal Bike Tour & Great Hudson Valley Pedal; Trailfinder Maps; Newsletters; Membership; bicycle; parks; trails; Tourism
  - Parks & Trails New York - working to expand, protect and promote a network of parks, trails and open spaces throughout our state for use and enjoyment by all, 2008 May 12
  - Parks & Trails New York - working to expand, protect and promote a network of parks, trails and open spaces throughout our state for use and enjoyment by all, 2008 May 16
  - Parks & Trails New York - working to expand, protect and promote a network of parks, trails and open spaces throughout our state for use and enjoyment by all, 2008 June 8
  - Parks & Trails New York - working to expand, protect and promote a network of parks, trails and open spaces throughout our state for use and enjoyment by all, 2008 July 13
  - Parks & Trails New York - working to expand, protect and promote a network of parks, trails and open spaces throughout our state for use and enjoyment by all, 2008 July 18
  - Parks & Trails New York - working to expand, protect and promote a network of parks, trails and open spaces throughout our state for use and enjoyment by all, 2008 July 24
  - Parks & Trails New York - working to expand, protect and promote a network of parks, trails and open spaces throughout our state for use and enjoyment by all, 2008 August 5
  - Parks & Trails New York - working to expand, protect and promote a network of parks, trails and open spaces throughout our state for use and enjoyment by all, 2008 August 6
  - Parks & Trails New York - working to expand, protect and promote a network of parks, trails and open spaces throughout our state for use and enjoyment by all, 2008 September 15
  - Parks & Trails New York - working to expand, protect and promote a network of parks, trails and open spaces throughout our state for use and enjoyment by all, 2008 October 18
  - Parks & Trails New York - working to expand, protect and promote a network of parks, trails and open spaces throughout our state for use and enjoyment by all, 2008 December 17
  - Parks & Trails New York - expanding, protecting and promoting a network of parks, trails and open spaces, 2009 February 6
  - Parks & Trails New York - expanding, protecting and promoting a network of parks, trails and open spaces, 2009 March 14
  - Parks & Trails New York - expanding, protecting and promoting a network of parks, trails and open spaces, 2009 August 19
  - Parks & Trails New York - expanding, protecting and promoting a network of parks, trails and open spaces, 2009 September 19
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2010 January 15
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2010 February 17
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2010 March 28
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2010 November 28
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2010 December 21
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2011 February 26
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2011 April 23
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2011 April 29
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2011 June 15
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2011 July 19
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2011 July 27
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2011 August 10
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2011 September 3
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2011 September 23
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2011 October 2
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2011 October 5
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2011 November 2
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2012 January 2
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2012 January 9
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2012 February 3
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2012 February 25
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2012 March 19
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2012 April 19
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2012 May 13
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2012 May 22
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2012 June 22
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2012 August 15
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2012 September 18
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2012 October 22
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2013 April 26
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2013 May 25
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2013 June 24
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2013 July 28
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2013 August 11
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2013 August 24
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2013 October 23
    Meta tag for description: Parks & Trails New York – protecting, expanding, and celebrating New York's parks and trails and strengthening the grassroots organizations that support them.
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2013 October 30
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2013 November 14
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2013 December 3
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2014 January 4
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2014 February 8
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2014 February 19
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2014 June 28
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2014 September 25
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2014 November 1
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2014 December 18
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2014 December 24
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2015 January 1
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2015 January 20
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2015 January 29
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2015 February 5
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2015 February 19
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2015 February 23
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2015 March 10
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2015 March 15
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2015 April 3
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2015 April 6
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2015 April 8
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2015 April 21
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2015 May 2
  - Parks & Trails New York, 2015 May 9
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2015 August 10
    Meta tag for keywords: parks, trails, canalway trail, biking, camping, new york state, hiking, outdoors,
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2015 August 13
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2015 August 25
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2015 September 3
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2015 September 5
  - 502 Bad Gateway, 2015 September 5
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2015 September 25
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2015 September 28
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2015 October 25
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2015 November 19
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2015 December 18
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2015 December 29
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 January 25
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 January 30
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 February 5
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 February 13
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 February 27
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 March 1
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 March 21
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 March 28
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 April 1
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 April 12
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 May 1
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 May 2
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 May 19
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 June 2
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 June 4
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 June 4
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 June 18
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 June 25
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 July 5
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 July 16
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 July 23
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 August 8
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 August 9
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 August 9
  - WARC file for Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 August 25
    crawl: 232507
    This item had no crawl rules.
    Crawl Times
    start_date: 2016-08-25T19:17:36Z
    original_start_date: 2016-08-25T19:17:36Z
    last_resumption: None
    processing_end_date: 2016-09-01T23:43:28Z
    end_date: 2016-09-01T01:45:24Z
    elapsed_ms: 179206750
    Crawl Types
    type: TEST_SAVED
    recurrence_type: NONE
    pdfs_only: False
    test: True
    Crawl Limits
    time_limit: 259200
    document_limit: None
    byte_limit: None
    crawl_stop_requested: None
    Crawl Results
    status: FINISHED
    discovered_count: 17198
    novel_count: 4431
    duplicate_count: 12767
    resumption_count: 0
    queued_count: 0
    downloaded_count: 17198
    download_failures: 61
    warc_revisit_count: 12767
    warc_url_count: 17187
    total_data_in_kbs: 786105
    duplicate_bytes: 403714028
    warc_compressed_bytes: 308069093
    Crawl Technical Details
    doc_rate: 0.1
    kb_rate: 4.0
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Researchers interested in data analysis with web archives may request a WARC file. WARC files are very large and difficult to work with. Your request may take time to process, and we may be unable to deliver your request remotely. Please consult an archivist if you are interested in advanced research with web archives.
  - WARC file for Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 August 25
  - WARC file for Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 August 26
    Crawl Rules
    Limit host facebook.com to 100 documents
    Limit host twimg.com to 100 documents
    Limit host twitter.com to 100 documents
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 September 16
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 September 17
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 September 19
  - WARC file for Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 October 7
    crawl: 241072
    start_date: 2016-10-07T20:17:04Z
    original_start_date: 2016-10-07T20:17:04Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-10-10T06:05:25Z
    end_date: 2016-10-10T02:01:37Z
    elapsed_ms: 193466011
    type: MONTHLY
    recurrence_type: MONTHLY
    test: False
    discovered_count: 17270
    novel_count: 2604
    duplicate_count: 14666
    downloaded_count: 17270
    download_failures: 59
    warc_revisit_count: 14666
    warc_url_count: 17259
    total_data_in_kbs: 823702
    duplicate_bytes: 633537414
    warc_compressed_bytes: 159758100
    doc_rate: 0.09
  - WARC file for Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 October 8
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 October 17
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 October 21
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 October 21
  - WARC file for Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 November 7
    crawl: 247620
    start_date: 2016-11-07T20:16:58Z
    original_start_date: 2016-11-07T20:16:58Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-11-10T02:15:16Z
    end_date: 2016-11-10T02:04:43Z
    elapsed_ms: 193651518
    discovered_count: 17494
    novel_count: 2122
    duplicate_count: 15372
    downloaded_count: 17494
    download_failures: 60
    warc_revisit_count: 15372
    warc_url_count: 17483
    total_data_in_kbs: 851251
    duplicate_bytes: 719930990
    warc_compressed_bytes: 91917269
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 December 1
  - WARC file for Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 December 7
    crawl: 253243
    start_date: 2016-12-07T20:25:55Z
    original_start_date: 2016-12-07T20:25:55Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-12-10T03:48:39Z
    end_date: 2016-12-10T03:33:47Z
    elapsed_ms: 198458916
    discovered_count: 17999
    novel_count: 3030
    duplicate_count: 14969
    downloaded_count: 17999
    download_failures: 63
    warc_revisit_count: 14969
    warc_url_count: 17988
    total_data_in_kbs: 994363
    duplicate_bytes: 702328874
    warc_compressed_bytes: 215110748
    kb_rate: 5.0
  - WARC file for Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 December 7
  - WARC file for Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2017 January 7
    crawl: 258888
    start_date: 2017-01-07T20:16:56Z
    original_start_date: 2017-01-07T20:16:56Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-01-10T06:56:57Z
    end_date: 2017-01-10T06:40:55Z
    elapsed_ms: 210224458
    discovered_count: 17499
    novel_count: 2527
    duplicate_count: 14972
    downloaded_count: 17499
    download_failures: 66
    warc_revisit_count: 14972
    warc_url_count: 17488
    total_data_in_kbs: 856668
    duplicate_bytes: 713902499
    warc_compressed_bytes: 92549221
    doc_rate: 0.08
  - WARC file for Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2017 January 8
  - WARC file for Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2017 February 7
    crawl: 265875
    start_date: 2017-02-07T20:18:04Z
    original_start_date: 2017-02-07T20:18:04Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-02-10T05:47:52Z
    end_date: 2017-02-10T05:35:16Z
    elapsed_ms: 206223907
    discovered_count: 17534
    novel_count: 2679
    duplicate_count: 14855
    downloaded_count: 17534
    download_failures: 58
    warc_revisit_count: 14855
    warc_url_count: 17523
    total_data_in_kbs: 845692
    duplicate_bytes: 683853274
    warc_compressed_bytes: 98159048
  - WARC file for Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2017 February 7
  - WARC file for Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2017 March 7
    crawl: 271770
    start_date: 2017-03-07T20:17:57Z
    original_start_date: 2017-03-07T20:17:57Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-03-10T20:36:52Z
    end_date: 2017-03-10T20:24:57Z
    elapsed_ms: 259207592
    status: FINISHED_TIME_LIMIT
    discovered_count: 20222
    novel_count: 3653
    duplicate_count: 16100
    queued_count: 469
    downloaded_count: 19753
    download_failures: 104
    warc_revisit_count: 16100
    warc_url_count: 19742
    total_data_in_kbs: 941383
    duplicate_bytes: 726469721
    warc_compressed_bytes: 21355462
    kb_rate: 3.0
  - WARC file for Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2017 March 7
  - WARC file for Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2017 March 8
  - WARC file for Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2017 March 10
  - WARC file for Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2017 April 7
    crawl: 289348
    start_date: 2017-04-07T20:17:20Z
    original_start_date: 2017-04-07T20:17:20Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-04-10T20:31:35Z
    end_date: 2017-04-10T20:17:49Z
    elapsed_ms: 259208574
    discovered_count: 20147
    novel_count: 3306
    duplicate_count: 16428
    queued_count: 413
    downloaded_count: 19734
    download_failures: 100
    warc_revisit_count: 16427
    warc_url_count: 19723
    total_data_in_kbs: 938689
    duplicate_bytes: 761778253
    warc_compressed_bytes: 105671229
  - WARC file for Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2017 April 7
  - WARC file for Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2017 April 7
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2017 May 4
  - WARC file for Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2017 May 7
    crawl: 299469
    start_date: 2017-05-07T20:16:48Z
    original_start_date: 2017-05-07T20:16:48Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-05-10T08:04:52Z
    end_date: 2017-05-10T07:53:38Z
    elapsed_ms: 214588187
    discovered_count: 18347
    novel_count: 2991
    duplicate_count: 15356
    downloaded_count: 18347
    download_failures: 80
    warc_revisit_count: 15355
    warc_url_count: 18336
    total_data_in_kbs: 990567
    duplicate_bytes: 809723985
    warc_compressed_bytes: 121245219
  - WARC file for Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2017 May 7
  - WARC file for Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2017 May 8
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2017 May 10
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2017 May 16
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2017 May 18
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2017 May 18
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 March 11
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2016 December 27
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2017 January 14
  - WARC file for Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2017 June 7
    crawl: 305700
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 100 for host facebook.com (created 2016-08-25, last updated 2017-05-04)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 100 for host twimg.com (created 2016-08-25, last updated 2017-05-04)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 100 for host twitter.com (created 2016-08-25, last updated 2017-05-04)
    start_date: 2017-06-07T20:17:05Z
    original_start_date: 2017-06-07T20:17:05Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-06-10T04:25:26Z
    end_date: 2017-06-10T04:14:46Z
    elapsed_ms: 201443930
    discovered_count: 7622
    novel_count: 3036
    duplicate_count: 4586
    downloaded_count: 7622
    download_failures: 125
    warc_revisit_count: 4586
    warc_url_count: 7611
    total_data_in_kbs: 653030
    duplicate_bytes: 508528750
    warc_compressed_bytes: 59257381
    doc_rate: 0.04
  - WARC file for Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2017 June 8
  - WARC file for Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2017 June 8
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2017 June 11
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2017 June 11
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2017 July 2
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2017 July 3
  - WARC file for Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2017 July 7
    crawl: 313156
    start_date: 2017-07-07T20:17:29Z
    original_start_date: 2017-07-07T20:17:29Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-07-11T19:56:06Z
    end_date: 2017-07-10T20:24:27Z
    elapsed_ms: 259408735
    discovered_count: 541623
    novel_count: 2153
    duplicate_count: 115188
    queued_count: 424282
    downloaded_count: 117341
    download_failures: 74
    warc_revisit_count: 115187
    warc_url_count: 117330
    total_data_in_kbs: 2603194
    duplicate_bytes: 2571096776
    warc_compressed_bytes: 10969543
    doc_rate: 0.45
    kb_rate: 10.0
  - Parks & Trails New York Homepage, 2017 July 18